<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?> 
<cheatsheet title="Create a JPA Project">
 <intro href="/org.eclipse.platform.doc.user/reference/ref-cheatsheets.htm">
  <description>
This cheat sheet will automatically launch wizards, perform actions, and guide you through the steps to create a JPA project. 
To learn more about using cheat sheets, or to see a list of available cheat sheets, click Help (?). 
To start work working on this cheat sheet click the "Click to Begin" button below. 
Let's get started!
  </description>
 </intro>
 <item title="Setup the enviroment" skip="true">
  <description>Your environment must be set up before you can perform the steps in this cheat sheet.
  Create a database connection.
  informationPending
  </description>
 </item>
 <item href="/org.eclipse.jdt.doc.user/tasks/tasks-12.htm" title="Create a JPA Project" skip="true">
  <action pluginId="org.eclipse.jdt.ui" class="org.eclipse.jdt.internal.ui.wizards.OpenProjectWizardAction" />
  <description>
First, you will need to create a JPA project.
If you already have a JPA project in your workspace that you would like to use, you may skip this step by clicking the "Click to Skip" button. If not, select File->New->Project... and choose JPA->JPA Project in the list. 
Complete the subsequent pages as required. 
The "New JPA Project" wizard is automatically displayed when you click the "Click to Perform" button.
  </description>
 </item>
 <item href="/org.eclipse.dali.doc.user/ref_add_persistence.htm" title="Adding Persistence">
  <action pluginId="org.eclipse.dali.ui" class="org.eclipse.dali.ui.actions.AddPersistenceNatureToIJavaProjectActionDelegate" param1=" " />
  <description>
Now you will "add persistence" to the project.
Right-click the Java project and select Java Persistence->Add Java Persistence.
Complete the Add Persistence dialog by specifying your database connection information. If you do not have an active database connection, click "Add Connections" to create one. 
The "Add Java Persistence" dialog is automatically displayed when you click the "Click to Perform" button. 
If you do not use the "Click to Perform" button below, click the "Click to Skip" button to advance to the next step.
  </description>
 </item>
 <item title="Adding JPA Libraries">
  <description>
To add your JPA library JARs, click "Configure the project build path." The Java Build Path" page of the Properties dialog appears. 
Add the JAP library JARs to your project. 
After adding the necessary libraries, click the "Click to Complete" button to advance to the next step.
  </description>
 </item>
 <item title="Creating a persistence.xml File" skip="true">
  <description>
To create a persistence.xml file for your project, select the "Create persistence.xml" option. Complete the remaining fields on the the Add Persistence dialog and click "Finish."  If you do not want to create a persistence.xml file, unselect the option and click the "Click to Skip" button to advance to the next step.
  </description>
 </item>
 <item title="Finish">
  <description>
Congratulations! You have successfully added persistence to your Java project. Complete the additional cheat sheets to add Java persistent entities and map those entities to database tables.
  </description>
 </item>
</cheatsheet>
