<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
    Copyright (c) 2007, 2019 IBM Corporation and others.
    This program and the accompanying materials
    are made available under the terms of the Eclipse Public License 2.0
    which accompanies this distribution, and is available at
    https://www.eclipse.org/legal/epl-2.0/

    SPDX-License-Identifier: EPL-2.0

    Contributors:
        IBM Corporation - initial API and implementation
 -->

<cheatsheet title="Create a JPA Project">
   <intro href="/org.eclipse.platform.doc.user/reference/ref-cheatsheets.htm">
      <description>
         This cheat sheet will automatically launch wizards, perform actions, and guide you through the steps to create a JPA project. 

To learn more about using cheat sheets, or to see a list of available cheat sheets, click Help (?). 
To start work working on this cheat sheet click the &quot;Click to Begin&quot; button below. 

Let&apos;s get started!
      </description>
   </intro>
   <item title="Setup the Environment" dialog="false" skip="true" href="/org.eclipse.datatools.doc.user/c_database_development_setup.html">
      <description>
         Your environment must be set up before you can perform the steps in this cheat sheet. 

Create a database profile and connect to the database.

The Database Connection dialog automatically appears when you click the &quot;Click to Perform&quot; button.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Create a JPA Project" dialog="false" skip="false" href="/org.eclipse.jpt.doc.user/task_create_new_project.htm">
      <description>
         Use the New Project Wizard to create a JPA project. 
Select <b>File-&gt;New-&gt;Project...</b> and choose <b>JPA-&gt;JPA Project</b> in the list. 

On the first page of the wizard, enter a project name and location, select your target runtime, and select a predefined project configuration.

Click <b>Next</b> to display the next page of the wizard.

The &quot;New JPA Project&quot; wizard is automatically displayed when you click the &quot;Click to Perform&quot; button.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Select Project Facet" dialog="false" skip="false" href="/org.eclipse.jst.j2ee.doc.user/topics/ph-projects.html">
      <description>
         Use the Project Facet page to select a predefined project configuration or specific specific facets to include in the project. 

Click &quot;Next&quot; to display the next page of the wizard.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Specify the JPA Facet" dialog="false" skip="false" href="/org.eclipse.jdt.doc.user/ref_jpa_facet.htm">
      <description>
         Use the JPA Facet page to specify the the vendor-specific JPA platform, the database connection to use, and the specific JPA implementation library. 

You can also specify if Dali should create an orm.xml file.

If you do not have an active database connection, click <b>Add Connections</b> to create one. 

If you do not have a defined JPA implementation library, click <b>Configure default JPA implementation library</b> or <b>Configure user libraries</b> to define one. 

Click <b>Finish</b> to complete the wizard and open the open the project.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Finish" dialog="false" skip="false">
      <description>
         Congratulations! You have successfully created a JPA project. Complete the additional cheat sheets to add Java persistent entities and map those entities to database tables.
      </description>
   </item>
</cheatsheet>
