<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- edited with XMLSpy v2006 sp2 U (http://www.altova.com) by FREDERICK (RICK) SAPIR (ORACLE BELMONT) -->
<cheatsheet title="Create a Persistent Entity">
	<intro href="/org.eclipse.platform.doc.user/reference/ref-cheatsheets.htm">
		<description>
This cheat sheet will automatically launch wizards, perform actions, and guide you through the steps to add a Java persistent entity to your Java project. 
To learn more about using cheat sheets or to see a list of available cheat sheets, click Help (?). 
To start work working on this cheat sheet, click the "Click to Begin" button below. 
Let's get started!
  </description>
	</intro>
	<item href="/org.eclipse.dali.doc.user/ref_persistence_perspective.htm" title="Open the Persistence Perspective" skip="true">
		<action pluginId="org.eclipse.ui.cheatsheets" class="org.eclipse.ui.internal.cheatsheets.actions.OpenPerspective" param1="org.eclipse.dali.ui.PersistencePerspective"/>
		<description>
When working with Java persistence, you should use the Persistence perspective. If you already have the Persistence perspective active, you may skip this step by clicking the "Click to Skip" button. 
If not, Select Window->Open Perspective->Other in the menubar at the top of the workbench. In the Select Perspectives dialog, select Persistence and click OK. This step changes the perspective to set up the Eclipse workbench for Java persistence development.
You can click the "Click to Perform" button to have the "Persistence" perspective opened automatically.
  </description>
	</item>
	<item href="/org.eclipse.dali.doc.user/create_new_entity.htm" title="Create a Persistent Entity" skip="true">
		<action pluginId="org.eclipse.ui.cheatsheets" class="org.eclipse.ui.internal.cheatsheets.actions.OpenPerspective" param1="org.eclipse.dali.ui.PersistencePerspective"/>
		<description>
To create a new Java persistent entity, use the Create Java Persistent Entity wizard. 
If you already have a Java persistent entity that you would like to use, you may skip this step by clicking the "Click to Skip" button. If not, select File->New->Other in the menubar at the top of the workbench. 
In the Select a Wizard dialog, select Java Persistence->Entity and click Next.
The "Java Persistent Entity" wizard is automatically displayed when you click the "Click to Perform" button.
  </description>
	</item>
	<item href="/org.eclipse.wst.datatools.connection.ui.doc.user/topics/ruidbconn_connpage.html" title="Add Database Connection" skip="true">
		<action pluginId="org.eclipse.ui.cheatsheets" class="org.eclipse.ui.internal.cheatsheets.actions.OpenPerspective" param1="org.eclipse.dali.ui.PersistencePerspective"/>
		<description>
If you already have a database connection in your workspace that you would like to use, you may skip this step by clicking the "Click to Skip" button. If not,  create a new database connection.
  </description>
	</item>
	<item href="/org.eclipse.dali.doc.user/ref_persistence_prop_view.htm" title="Specifying Persistence Properties">
		<action pluginId="org.eclipse.ui.cheatsheets" class="org.eclipse.ui.internal.cheatsheets.actions.OpenPerspective" param1="org.eclipse.dali.ui.PersistencePerspective"/>
		<description>
Now you will associate the entity with a database table.
In the Persistence Properties view of the selected entity, use the "Table Name" field to select the database table to which the entity maps.
The "Persistence Properties" view is automatically displayed when you click the "Click to Perform" button.
  </description>
	</item>
	<item title="Finish">
		<description>
Congratulations! You have successfully added an Java persistent entity to your Java project. Complete the additional cheat sheets to map the entity's fields to database tables.
  </description>
	</item>
</cheatsheet>
